export const mockContent = `[
  {
    "question": "In what in-game book series is Emhyr var Emreis detailed?",
    "options": ["History of Gwent", "Redanian Intelligence", "The Great Wars", "Emperors of Nilfgaard"],
    "correctAnswer": "Emperors of Nilfgaard"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches Geralt advanced combat in Kaer Morhen?",
    "options": ["Eskel", "Vesemir", "Lambert", "Ciri"],
    "correctAnswer": "Vesemir"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which character is known as 'The White Flame'?",
    "options": ["Radovid", "Eredin", "Emhyr var Emreis", "Ciri"],
    "correctAnswer": "Emhyr var Emreis"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Geralt's profession?",
    "options": ["Knight", "Monster Hunter", "Sorcerer", "Assassin"],
    "correctAnswer": "Monster Hunter"
  },
  {
    "question": "What item allows Geralt to see in the dark?",
    "options": ["Magic Lamp", "Witcher Sense", "Cat Potion", "Night Vision Goggles"],
    "correctAnswer": "Cat Potion"
  },
  {
    "question": "At what age do Witchers undergo the Trial of Grasses?",
    "options": ["21", "16", "12", "10"],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the primary currency in the game?",
    "options": ["Golds", "Orens", "Crowns", "Ducats"],
    "correctAnswer": "Crowns"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the 'Igni' sign do?",
    "options": ["Heals", "Protects", "Produces fire", "Teleports"],
    "correctAnswer": "Produces fire"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is NOT a higher vampire's notable trait in games?",
    "options": ["Ability to control minds", "Shapeshifting", "Immunity to sunlight", "Toxic breath"],
    "correctAnswer": "Toxic breath"
  },
  {
    "question": "What secret society does Sigi Reuven alias belong to?",
    "options": ["Order of the Flaming Rose", "The Lodge of Sorceresses", "The Wild Hunt", "Big Four of Novigrad"],
    "correctAnswer": "Big Four of Novigrad"
  }
]`;

export const BASE_PRICE_OPTIONS = [
  { label: 'Nobie', value: 0.00001, description: 'A super light trial' },
  { label: 'Acolyte', value: 0.0001, description: 'A light trial' },
  { label: 'Adept', value: 0.001, description: 'A worthy challenge' },
  { label: 'Master', value: 0.01, description: 'A trial of legends' },
];
